{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550241248307","data":{"timestamp":" 1550241248307"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_173347"," gameId":" 6bc2155c-23cf-4f58-8487-8e88b4ab9c47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_11-6-14"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550241253117","data":{"timestamp":" 1550241253117"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_173347"," gameId":" 6bc2155c-23cf-4f58-8487-8e88b4ab9c47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_10-6-14"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550241258601","data":{"timestamp":" 1550241258601"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_173347"," gameId":" 6bc2155c-23cf-4f58-8487-8e88b4ab9c47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-15"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550241265285","data":{"timestamp":" 1550241265284"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_173347"," gameId":" 6bc2155c-23cf-4f58-8487-8e88b4ab9c47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-15"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550241270145","data":{"timestamp":" 1550241270145"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_173347"," gameId":" 6bc2155c-23cf-4f58-8487-8e88b4ab9c47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-5-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550241277287","data":{"timestamp":" 1550241277287"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_173347"," gameId":" 6bc2155c-23cf-4f58-8487-8e88b4ab9c47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-5-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550241282625","data":{"timestamp":" 1550241282625"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_173347"," gameId":" 6bc2155c-23cf-4f58-8487-8e88b4ab9c47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550241287641","data":{"timestamp":" 1550241287641"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_173347"," gameId":" 6bc2155c-23cf-4f58-8487-8e88b4ab9c47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-15"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550241292604","data":{"timestamp":" 1550241292604"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_173347"," gameId":" 6bc2155c-23cf-4f58-8487-8e88b4ab9c47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-15-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550241365976","data":{"timestamp":" 1550241365976"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_173347"," gameId":" 6bc2155c-23cf-4f58-8487-8e88b4ab9c47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_16-10-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}